<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Zaal, NLP as a service for Persian langauge</title>
    <link>http://getzaal.com/service/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Zaal, NLP as a service for Persian langauge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://getzaal.com/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Document Classification</title>
      <link>http://getzaal.com/service/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getzaal.com/service/service2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Classifiying documents automatically is one of the main activities for effectively managing text and unstructured information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also referred to as categorization, clustering or text classification, automatic document classification allows you to divide and organize text based on a set of predefined categories that allow rapid, easy retrieval of information in the search phase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assignning meaningful topics to your texts never been easier. Zaal enables you to
automatically find the abstract topics of your text using a RESTful API.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyword Extraction</title>
      <link>http://getzaal.com/service/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getzaal.com/service/service4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Extracting keywords that could be good representatives of a document is one of the most important tasks when dealing with corpora of text. Readers could benefit heavily from keywords because they can judge more quickly whether the text is worth reading or not. Website creators benefit from keywords because they can group similar content by its topics. These are just a few benefits of keword extraction process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using Zaal you could extract meaningful keywords seamlessly and smoothly using a RESTful API.
For more Info please see the &lt;code&gt;live demo&lt;/code&gt; section.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>http://getzaal.com/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getzaal.com/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Using machine learning and one of its thriving domain (i.e. deep learning) we built a system to analyze sentiments associated with various texts in order to get actionable insights where texts bear subjective tonality such as comments and reviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zaal provides two types of sentiment analysis methods, &lt;strong&gt;Document Level&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Aspect Based&lt;/strong&gt;.
In the former comments and reviews are classfied into &lt;code&gt;negative&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;neutral&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;poistive&lt;/code&gt; in a hollistic approach but in the latter, a comment or review is broken into meaningful parts that each part could have its specific tonality about something (i.e. an aspect).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word Embbeding</title>
      <link>http://getzaal.com/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getzaal.com/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Using vector space models (VSMs) we can represent (embed) words in a continuous vector space where semantically similar words and phrases are mapped to nearby points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View your categorical data set from different dimensions using Zaal. Find semantically similar
words in a corpus of text using Zaal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>